exploitedcollegegirls.com 2019-12-19

# ExCoGi - Exploited College Girls -

## TERMS

Please read the Terms and Conditions (known and referred to as "agreement") for ExploitedCollegeGirls.com (also referred to as "this site", "we", "us", "ExCoGi", "ECG") carefully before joining or in any way using or interacting with this site. By browsing this site, or completing the membership form and purchasing a subscription, or interacting with this site or portions thereof in any other way, you (also known and referred to as "visitor" or "member" or "subscriber") state that you have read and agree to be bound by this agreement in its entirety.

Access to this site is intended solely for people who are of legal age in the jurisdiction where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (21 in AL, MS, NE, and WY), who wish to access visual images, audio sounds, and verbal descriptions of a sexually oriented and frankly erotic nature. Materials available within this site may include depictions that are visually graphic in nature and portrayals of nudity or sexual acts and should not be accessed by anyone who is not of legal age in the jurisdiction where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (21 in AL, MS, NE, and WY), by anyone who finds such material offensive in nature, or by anyone who simply does not wish to be exposed to such materials. By visiting this site or purchasing a membership or access rights, you are implicitly making the following statements: "I affirm and swear that as of this moment, under penalty of Perjury, I am of legal age in the jurisdiction where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (21 in AL, MS, NE, and WY). I will not permit any persons who are not of legal age in the jurisdiction where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (21 in AL, MS, NE, and WY) to view or access in any way any materials found on this website. I understand that by accessing this website, I will be exposed to materials that may include but are not limited to, visual images, audio sounds, and verbal descriptions of a sexually oriented and frankly erotic nature, portrayals of nudity, and sexual acts. I affirm that I am not offended by such materials, and that such materials are legal in my community. I am volunteering to view, hear, and access such materials on my own volition, and I choose to do so because I want to view/read/hear or otherwise access such materials for my own enjoyment, information or entertainment. My choice is a manifestation of my interest in such matters, which is healthy and normal, and is also held by most adults in my area. I am completely familiar with the standards held in my community, and the material I expect to access in this site falls within these standards. In my experience, the average adult in my community accepts the consumption of such materials by willing adults in circumstances such as this, which offer reasonable insulation from the materials for minors, and unwilling adults. Adults in my community will accept the standards displayed within this site, and will not find any of the material patently offensive."

The material contained in this website is non-violent adult material containing sexually explicit situations. Viewing by, possession of, sale or distribution to minors is against the law. Exercising our first amendment rights, this material has been made by adults, and is intended ONLY for adults who wish to view it. It is unlawful to continue if the fore mentioned material is illegal, outlawed or may violate community standards where you are viewing said material. The following material represents staged, scripted, and fictional accounts of sexual relationships of adults. All performers in the following material are intended to be portrayed and understood as fully consenting adults that are performing of their own free will. This material is meant to serve as a visual record of the methods of interpersonal and sexual relationships. However, please note that these fictional accounts do not always exhibit safe sex, or the full range of real life emotions and relationships. Moreover, this material is created to inform viewers of the wide range of adult relationships. It presents the idea that these are important aspects of adult relationships and that sexual conduct is enjoyable in various forms of expression.

***BILLING AND CANCELLATIONS:** All membership packages will automatically renew upon expiration unless your subscription is cancelled prior to the end of the current subscription package term, or unless you selected a non-recurring type of memmbership, such as a 90-day non-recurring membership plan. Membership cancellations will not be accepted via email but must be cancelled at [https://support.ccbill.com](https://support.ccbill.com/) or [https://epoch.com](https://epoch.com/) or [https:/webbilling.com](https://www.webbilling.com/), depending on which of these billing companies charged your credit card or bank account. It is important that you keep the welcome email you receive from the billing company after you join.  
*REFUND POLICY: refunds requests are handled on a case by case basis and determined by ExCoGi or the billing company, or as required by law. 

**You further agree to the following:**

*As a member you are responsible for paying membership fees pertaining to the specific billing package purchased. Your credit card (or bank account, if you selected to pay your membership fee that way) will be billed immediately after purchase. All billing is processed by a trusted third party billing company, either CCBill.com, Epoch.com, or Webbillingcom. All billing questions and cancellation requests must be addressed directly with the billing company that processed your credit card or bank account.  
*Members user name and password are not transferable and are not to be distributed to others. This site monitors memberships, user names and passwords and distribution and transfer of said information will result in immediate suspension of service and possible further legal action. ExploitedCollegeGirls.com.com under law must hold the member liable for unauthorized breach of membership.  
*ExploitedCollegeGirls.com reserves the right to block user names, IP addresses, and entire geographic locations for any violations of its terms of service, for security reasons, and for any other reason its operators feel appropriate.   
*ExploitedCollegeGirls.com reserves the right to limit the amount of content a member can downloaded per day.  
*ExploitedCollegeGirls.com may, at its sole discretion, offer paying subscribers ("members") access to members areas of third party sites ("bonus sites"). Member understands and agrees that ExploitedCollegeGirls.com may remove or limit such access at any time for any reason, and that member is not eligible for any refunds or any other form of compensation should access to bonus sites or content be revoked, reduced, limited, or altered in any way.   
*Member understands that by entering a bonus site or any other third party site to which ExploitedCollegeGirls.com links, the terms of use and privacy policy of that bonus or third party site applies to member. Member is advised to thoroughly read the terms of use and privacy policy of any site before entering or interacting with it in any way.   
*Member agrees to not contact the webmaster or operators of a bonus site to which he has access to via the ExploitedCollegeGirls.com members area, but instead will contact the ExploitedCollegeGirls.com webmaster directly with any questions or concerns. The ExploitedCollegeGirls.com webmaster will then forward such questions or concerns to the appropriate webmaster or operator at his or her discretion.   
*Member understands that ExploitedCollegeGirls.com as well as any of the bonus sites or third party sites to which he has access to via the ExploitedCollegeGirls.com members area may at any time block or otherwise refuse him access, block his user name or IP address, and take any other measures deemed fit. For example, if a ExploitedCollegeGirls.com member violates terms of use of a bonus site, the bonus site as well as ExploitedCollegeGirls.com may block that member from accessing the bonus sites members area or ExploitedCollegeGirls.coms members area.   
*The member agrees to hold harmless ExploitedCollegeGirls.com, its' parent companies, subsidiaries, owners, officers, affiliates, and employees, including without limitation under any and all courses of action. Any liability due to the member will be limited to the amount paid by a member for the preceding 6 months.  
*ExploitedCollegeGirls.com may offer services from third party providers. Unless specifically stated to be "free", you should assume that the service is not free and any charges are your responsibility.   
*It is the member's sole responsibility to inform ExploitedCollegeGirls.com in regards to changes in the method of payment or changes in credit card details once their card has expired for continuation of service.  
* It is the sole responsible of members to acquire all equipment (hardware and Software) necessary to access, navigate, and view the material contained in this site.  
* Without prejudice, ExploitedCollegeGirls.com reserves the right to cancel or refuse membership to any individual or entity at any time.  
*ExploitedCollegeGirls.com reserves the right to deny memberships or access to visitors from certain countries or locales for any reason.  
*Without limitation ExploitedCollegeGirls.com.com does not infer any warranty to any aspect of the service be it a service provided directly by ExploitedCollegeGirls.com or a 3rd party source contained herein.  
*All motion pictures, still images, sounds, text, and any and all other material contained in this site are the sole property of ExploitedCollegeGirls.com and are not to be copied, disseminated, sold, or distributed in any form without the prior written consent of ExploitedCollegeGirls.com  
*This Agreement in its entirety contains the entire agreement between the member and ExploitedCollegeGirls.com.com. Any questions regarding this agreement should be sent to admin1 (at) exploitedcollegegirls (dot) com. The laws of the United States of America shall govern this agreement.  
These terms of conditions may be changed, modified or edited at any time. It is your responsibility to verify terms of conditions intermittently to see if there has been any change. 

:::

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy has been **updated May 25, 2018.** By using our services in any way on or after that date, you’ll be agreeing to this privacy policy and all revisions. Some new additions to this privacy policy are only applicable to EU residents, or who are otherwise covered by Europe's General Data Protection Regulations ("GDPR" for short henceforth). You agree to check this privacy policy for any changes or updates each time you visit this site.

The Mayflower Group, LLC, 1155 E Twain Ave - Ste #180-17, Las Vegas, NV 89135 operates the https://exploitedcollegegirls.com website, hereinafter “Service” or “we” or “us” or “site”or “ExCoGi”.

Read this privacy policy carefully – your access and use of this site means you have read and understood and agreed to all terms. If you do not agree to all parts of this privacy policy, please cease use of this site or any parts thereof immediately. Further, do not submit any personal data, or email us, or fill out contact forms.   
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information. Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified by, and it does not include data that has been anonymized or pseudonymized.   
We also address GDPR specific issues such as data retention, deletion requests, what data we and our third party partners gather, and more. Remember that GDPR only is applicable if you are located in the European Union.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at https://exploitedcollegegirls.com/free/terms.html, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

## Information Collection and Use

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) states that personal data should be collected, processed, and retained for no longer than is necessary for the purpose it was obtained for. When we mention any retention periods in this document below, it refers to retention of data from EU subjects only. Please carefully read below what data we collect directly, and what data third party services collect on our behalf, in particular billing companies. For third party data collection, we provide a general overview of their data gathering and use practices, but we can't guarantee this overview is comprehensive. To find out the full extend of their data gathering, storage, and retention practice, please contact each third party service directly.   
This policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through other means such as any other website operated by us, or any third party or affiliates.

## Log Data

Like almost every other web site, we automatically collect information that your browser sends to us, which is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser version, pages of this site you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, the site or URL you were on before you came to this site, and other statistics, depending on your browser and the server software. This information is automatically captured by servers, even if you do not become a paying member or otherwise interact with the site. Merely by visiting this site, the servers capture this data and stores it for up to 30 days, longer if required by law. This information is needed to investigate or prevent any hacking or other illegal activities, provide customer service, help us learn how, why, when, and where visitors use this site or portions thereof, and help us allocate the necessary resources to ensure a smooth experience for our members.   
This information is stored on the server in log files, which are accessible by the hosting company , as well as the webmaster and support agents of this site via a password protected administration interface on the server.

## Transaction and Financial Data

If you become a paying member of this site, additional information will be obtained (“Transaction/Financial Data”) about you, most of which you voluntarily agree to provide, but some may be obtained without your explicit input. During the payment process, a third party payment process ("Biller") will require you to input your name, address, credit card or bank account data, zip code, email address, and other personally identifiable information. They may also automatically capture your IP address and browser information without your input. Exactly what data a Biller captures and what they do with it and for how long depends on the Biller, and you need to contact the Biller's sites to find out more. Please scroll down to the Third Party section for more detailed information, including GDPR-related rights if you are located in the EU, such as what data is used, by whom, and how to request deletion, etc.   
This site does not itself host your credit card data, but it does receive your user name and encrypted password and IP address, which are stored in a database. This is required in order for you to be able to log in to the site. Further, the site may obtain any other information you provided to the Billers such as your full name, address, referring URL (the URL that referred you this site, which, if it is a URL or website operated by an affiliate of this site, will be paid for this referral), and IP address, which will be stored in a separate secure database.  
All information described above will generally remain in the site's databases or Biller's system indefinitely or until you request deletion of that data, however the actual retention time varies by Biller. Remember that in order for you to be able to log in or receive any support or services, we must have this information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.  
Our website uses these "cookies" to collection information and to improve our Service. You do not have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies. Merely by visiting this site, cookies will be stored on your computer. You can delete these cookies at any time by going into your browser settings and deleting them. If you choose to refuse our cookies , you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. If you become a paying member and wish to log in to the members area, you must have cookies enabled for the duration of your visit to the members area. You are welcome to delete the cookies from your browser after your visit , but this may make logging in later less convenient for you.

If you contact us via any of our contact forms, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, user name (if a member) and email address. Further, our forms automatically collect your IP address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you, and we may try to match this information with data our billing companies have stored about you in order to verify your membership, location, or in order to assist with any technical or other issues you may have contacted us or the billing companies about. All submissions whether via a contact form or email can be accessed by the webmaster of this site, and its owners, and its designated third parties such as our third party technical support service. When you submit a form you also give us permission to share this information with the hosting company, Biller, customer support agent, and third party marketing service in order for us to investigate fraud, provide customer or technical service, investigate technical issues such as download or streaming video problems, and to offer additional products and services via email campaigns. You can opt out of any email campaigns at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link on the bottom of any marketing email we or our designated third party email marketing services provider send to you. Our contact forms are provided by a third party service called JotForm.com, and you can read about how we use their service in the Third Party Service Providers section below.

## Third Party Service Providers

We employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To provide billing services for memberships;
  * To facilitate the log-in and authentication process for members.
  * To provide customer or technical support;
  * To enforce this site's Terms of Service/ Terms of Use
  * To offer additional products and services such as live webcam shows.
  * To gather demographic and technical information about our visitors and members; and
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to various types of information, although only billing companies will have information such as your name, address, email address, payment information, etc, and only if you voluntarily provide it by purchasing a membership or by contacting them. We also employ tracking services from Google Analytics and Hotjar, but this data does not include your name, address, or other personal data, with exception of your IP address in the case of Hotjar, and limited browser data such as type and version number. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf, which is detailed below. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose unless required by law. Each third party in turn has their own storage and retention policies. We are not always able to delete your information on your behalf, and you will need to contact each third party service directly should you wish to have them delete your information.

  * **CCBill;** provides billing services to members; CCBill is a third party service and whereas this site uses CCBill to process credit cards and bank account payments for its memberships on the site's behalf, this site does not have the ability to control precisely what data CCBill obtains or how long it retains it. Generally speaking, when you purchase a membership, CCBill will ask for your full name, billing address, email address, phone number, and credit card or bank account details. It may also capture your IP address and browser information automatically in order to prevent fraud. The webmaster and support agents of this site have access to this data, but not your credit card or banking data. A copy of most data you provide to CCBill (but not credit card or bank account info) will also be transferred to this site's statistical and administration software. This is needed in order for the site to obtain financial information, calculate referral fee payments to its affiliates, understand sources of its web traffic, conduct more concise marketing, and investigate fraud. To learn more about their privacy policy and how GDPR subjects can exercise their rights, please see CCBill's site:https://www.ccbill.com/gdpr/.
  * **Epoch Billing (“Epoch”);** provides billing services to members; Epoch is a third party payment service and whereas this site uses Epoch to process credit cards , PayPal, and bank account payments for its memberships on the site's behalf, this site does not have the ability to control precisely what data Epoch obtains or how long it retains it. Generally speaking, when you purchase a membership, Epoch will ask for your full name, billing address, email address, phone number, and credit card or bank account details. It may also capture your IP address and browser information automatically in order to prevent fraud. The webmaster and support agents of this site have access to this data, but not your credit card or banking data. A copy of most data you provide to Epoch (but not credit card or bank account info) will also be transferred to this site's statistical and administration software. This is needed in order for the site to obtain financial information, calculate referral fee payments to its affiliates, understand sources of its web traffic, conduct more concise marketing, and investigate fraud. To learn more about their privacy policy and how GDPR subjects can exercise their rights, please see Epoch 's site:https://epoch.com/privacy.html .
  * **Webbilling;** provides billing services to members; Webbilling is a third party billing service that specializes in processing EU-specific payment methods such as GiroPay, DirectDebit, DirectPay, and others. This site uses Webbilling to process certain types of payment for its memberships on the site's behalf, but this site does not have the ability to control precisely what data Webbilling obtains or how long it retains it. Generally speaking, when you purchase a membership, Webbilling will ask for your full name, billing address, email address, phone number, bank account details. It may also capture your IP address and browser information automatically in order to prevent fraud. The webmaster and support agents of this site have access to this data, but not your credit card or banking data. Your name, membership user name and password, and how much you paid for your membership will also be transferred to this site's statistical and administration software. This is needed in order for the site to obtain financial information, calculate referral fee payments to its affiliates, understand sources of its web traffic, conduct more concise marketing, and investigate fraud. To learn more about their privacy policy and how GDPR subjects can exercise their rights, please see Webbilling 's site:https://www.webbilling.com/en/privacy.html
  * **Google Analytics;** provides analytical information about people visiting or otherwise interacting with this site, what search terms they used to find the site, what pages they visit, how long they visit the site, and other aspects. Information in Google Analytics is stored for 14 months. Google Analytics does not capture or show us IP addresses, names, or any other personally identifiable data. You can ready more about exactly what data Google Analytics captures and what it does with it, and opt out here: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245
  * **HotJar.com;** provides analytical information about people visiting or otherwise interacting with this site, which parts of a page they click or hover over, which links are clicked, what pages they visit, how long they visit the site, and other aspects. Hotjar does capture IP addresses but anonymizes it. Information in Hotjar is stored for 120 days. You can learn more about what data Hotjar collects and for what purpose, and opt out, delete, and amend your data here: https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/gdpr-commitment .
  * **Sites Support;** https://sites.support. This is our dedicated third party technical and customer support provider. Their support agents have access to your Biller data (user name and password, IP address, physical address, referring affiliate, if applicable, join date, recurring payment dates, but not credit card information). Sites Support has access to your access logs, which means they can see when you logged in,what IP address you had when you logged in, and if there were any log-in errors. They also have access to server logs and are authorized to communicate with out hosting company in order to obtain logs information as discussed in the beginning of this policy. Further, the contact forms on Sites Support automatically capture your IP address and browser version; Sites Support retains all data for 30 days. If you wish to have any data deleted from Sites Support, simply create a new ticket.
  * **Bonus Sites;** when you purchase a membership to this site, you also get free access to the members areas of several other sites, some of which are not owned or operated by us at all. In order to be able to offer you this service for free, we must share your login credentials with those sites. However, this is done automatically via proprietary code that is not accessible to third parties, and your user name and password are encrypted during the process. The bonus site can, however, see your user name and IP address in their own server logs if they wish to look for it. By becoming a member you explicitly agree that the bonus sites are authorized to see your user name and IP address. If you don't want this, you must not purchase a membership. We give you free access to the following bonus sites (which can see your user name and IP address in their own visitor logs): BackroomCastingCouch.com, BlackAmbush.com, NebraskaCoeds.com, SouthbeachCoeds.com, SpringbreakLife.com EuroCoeds.com, AfterhoursExposed.com.   
This list may change at any time for any reason. Members are responsible for reading the privacy policy for each site. Further, each bonus site may offer you additional products or services, included some that are provided by third parties, such as access to live cam shows provided by third-party camsites. We do not have control and are not responsible for any such content or functionality or offers.
  * **Live webcam services;** The members area may offer you access to live webcam performers through https://ecgcams.com. This service is provided by a third party company, ICF Technology Inc (henceforth “Streamate”). which is solely responsible for the functionality and privacy aspects. By visiting ECGCams.com or clicking any links or buttons in the members area such as “LIVE GIRLS” or similarly named items, Streamate may begin tracking you and your activities, and offer ways for you to pay for services. Use of this service is entirely voluntary and you can avoid being tracked by Streamate by not visiting the webcam portions of this site. You can find their privay policy here: https://ecgcams.com/privacy.html
  * **Jotform.com;** Our contact forms are provided by a third party service called JotForm.com, which receives information described above and stores it on their own servers until we or they delete it. The forms employ encryption when you send it. Once your form reaches Jotform's servers, an email with that information is also dispatched to the recipient, which may be the webmaster or support person for this site, depending on which form you filled out. Jotform promises that it does not sell or otherwise give away your information. You can read Jotforms full privacy policy here: https://www.jotform.com/privacy/
  * **Email Marketing;** We work with a third party service, XFC Inc, 1930 Village Center Circle Ste 3 #1093, Las Vegas, Nevada, 81934, henceforth “XFC”. Anyone who became a member of this site prior to May 25 2018 agreed to receive email communication. After that date, EU subjects need to explicitly consent to receive marketing emails. Note that operational emails such as account warnings and notifications etc, do not require explicit consent. We obtain member email addresses from the billing companies, or our own email capture forms, and add them to our mailing list (provided we have consent to do so), which is operated by XFC. From time to time, recipients of that mailing list may receive emails from us such as special offers to join this or other sites at discounts, or other marketing offers. You may opt out of these emails at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link on the bottom of any of these emails, or by contacting us at privacy@exploitedcollegegirls.com and telling us the email address you wish to remove from the mailing list.

## International Data Transfer

This site is hosted in the United States. If you are located in a non-US jurisdiction, for example in the European Economic Area ("EEA") / European Union ("EU"), you agree that the provision of personal data or other access or use of this site constitutes your consent to the transfer of such data/information, including personal data, to the United States, a jurisdiction that may or may not provide the same level of data protection compared to the laws in your home country.Security

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. The servers this site is hosted on are monitored 24/7 and are scanned daily for malware and viruses. Further, we employ various proprietary and open source technologies to prevent hackers or malicious scripts from accessing restricted server areas, including but not limited to any of your personal information that may be stored. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security

## Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 18, 21 in some jurisdictions. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from persons under 18. In case we discover that a person under 18 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us immediately so that we can take necessary actions as soon as possible. We employ the RTA (“Restricted To Adults”) label on our site in order for parents to make it easier to block our site. You can learn more about this at http://rtalabel.org

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

## GDPR Rights – Additional Granular Information

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) offers changes to data privacy for any person or company located in the European Union. The purpose is to give subjects greater control over their personal information, including the right to actively consent to every use of personal data and the right to limit that use, as well as “the right to be forgotten”, the right to have their data portable, and the right to seek damages should they suffer from misuse/breach of their data.

As you can see by reading our privacy policy, this site itself only keeps very little personally identifiable data about you, in particular if you only visit the site but don't purchase a membership or use any contact form. The bulk of data is stored by our third parties such as the billing companies, which captures and stores this information from you if you purchase a membership, only some of which they will send to us (user name, encrypted password) - and this is necessary in order for you to have an active membership. When you submit a request to have your data deleted, we will begin deleting your data from servers and systems we have direct control over, and inform third parties such as the billing companies of your request as well. However, it may often be faster and more thorough for you to contact a billing company directly to have them delete your data.

If you are an EU resident and wish to have your data deleted, [fill out this form](https://form.jotform.com/81440772785161 "GDPR Form") or email privacy@exploitedcollegegirls.com with your full name, IP address, and email address you used to sign up or otherwise interact with this site. Please note that once we delete all your data, this will include data you provide via the contact form or email. Therefore we cannot contact you to let you know that this data has been deleted.

If you wish to obtain any personally identifiable data we have of you in an electronically portable format, you may request that at no cost [here](https://form.jotform.com/81440772785161 "GDPR Form"). You will receive a spreadsheet or text document with any information we have as soon as possible.   
**Note:** we do not respond to requests for deletion or portable data or any other GDPR-related requests from anyone located outside the EU, or otherwise not covered by GDPR. Further, we are not obligated to restrict retention of any data of persons not located in the EU or covered by GDPR, and we reserve the right to keep such data for any period we deem necessary, prudent, and lawful.

## Do Not Track Policy

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference users can set in most browsers. How you do this depends on your browser. It is not legally required for a site or service to honor this request, and many sites, such as ours, don't have the ability to recognize or respond to any DNT requests. In other words, DNT does not work on this site.

## California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code permits users of this site who are California residents to request certain information about the site's disclosure of personal information to third parties for the purpose of direct marketing. You can email privacy@exploitedcollegegirls.com to make this request, and to opt-out from disclosure of your information to third parties for marketing purposes. (California residents only).   
This affects marketing ONLY. You may still receive relevant account or billing information, or other select offers from the site in accordance with California law.

## Legal successor

In the event this sites undergoes a merger, restructuring, buyout, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy, liquidation, or other sale or transfer of any or all assets, any personal information held by this site may be among the assets transferred or sold. Should a sale or other described event occur this site will take reasonable steps to ensure that the entity to which this information is transferred uses it in a manner consistent with this privacy policy.
